unittus.com 2016-06-08

# Unittus | The First People Search and Social Network in the World. Join Unittus.

This Privacy Policy ('Policy') explains how information about you is collected, used and disclosed by Unittus, Inc. and its subsidiaries and affiliates ('Unittus,' 'we' or 'us'). This Policy applies to all of the websites (including www.Unittus.com), products, applications (including mobile applications and applications and pages) operated by Unittus and services offered by Unittus wherever this Policy is displayed (collectively, the 'Services').

Please note that we are based in the United States of America. As such, any personal information you provide us with or is collected by us as detailed below is transferred to and processed by us in the United States of America (or other countries). By registering or subscribing to the Services, you agree to this transfer and processing.

####  Information We Collect

**Information You Provide.** When you register or subscribe to any of our Services, we may collect a variety of information, including your name, birth date, photographs, email address, password, phone number, including mobile phone number, billing information, credit card information and other contact or demographic information you provide. We also collect other profile data such as your personal interests and background, gender, age, geographical location and physical characteristics and any content or other communications you provide or make in connection with your use of the Services. We may also obtain information from other sources and combine that with information we collect through our Services.

**Information Automatically Collected.** When you access our Services, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website, such as your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, platform type, the site from which you came and the site to which you are going when you leave our website, date and time stamp and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser or your account. When you access our Services using a mobile device, we may receive or collect your mobile device ID (often referred to as UDID), mobile carrier, device manufacturer and phone number. We also collect information about your usage of, and activity on, our Services. We may associate information we automatically collect with your personal information. We and service providers acting on our behalf, such as Google Analytics, use this information to understand and analyze trends, to administer our Services, to gather demographic information about our user base and to deliver you a more personalized experience.

**Cookies and Other Technologies.** Our Services, email messages and advertisements may use 'cookies' and other technologies such as pixel tags and Web beacons. 'Cookies' are small data files stored on your hard drive by a website. Among other things, cookies help us improve our Services and your experience. We use cookies to see which areas and features are popular and to count visits to our websites. We may also use cookies and other technologies to serve advertisements to you on our Services or on sites other than our websites. Web beacons and pixel tags are electronic images that may be used on our Services or in our emails. We use Web beacons and pixel tags to deliver cookies, count visits, understand usage and campaign effectiveness, prevent fraud and to tell if an email or advertisement has been opened and acted upon.

**Third Party Advertisers.** Any advertisers and advertising networks (which include third party ad servers, ad agencies, ad technology vendors and research firms) that serve ads or provide offers to our users, on our Services or on sites other than our websites, may also use their own cookies, web beacons, pixels and other tracking technologies. Such tracking technologies are governed by the privacy policies of the entities placing the ads, and are not subject to this Policy. You can visit networkadvertising.org to see a list of advertising networks that typically serve these kinds of ads and to exercise your choice for those advertising networks. We do not control these advertisers or advertising networks or any other third parties whose websites may be linked from our Services or their practices. We recommend that your review the privacy statements of all third-party websites you visit.

####  Use of Personal Information We Collect

We use the personal information we collect for purposes described in this Policy or disclosed to you on or in connection with our Services. Ways we may use information about you include:  

  * to operate, provide, maintain, develop, deliver, protect and improve our Services, products, applications, content and advertising and develop new products and services;
  * to maintain and administer your Unittus account;
  * to maintain and display your Unittus Uprofile;
  * to respond to your comments and questions and provide customer service;
  * to detect and prevent abusive, fraudulent, malicious or potentially illegal activities, and to protect the rights, safety or property of Unittus or our users;
  * to enforce our Terms of Use agreement;
  * to keep you posted on our latest product or service announcements, software updates, security alerts and any technical notices;
  * to communicate with you about new contests, promotions and rewards, upcoming events and other news about products and services offered by Unittus and our selected partners;
  * to provide you with confirmation of purchases, invoices, support and administrative messages or notice about changes to our terms, conditions or policies;
  * to administer any contests or promotions;
  * to perform other functions as otherwise described to you at the time of collection; and
  * to link or combine information about you with other information we get from third parties to help understand your needs and provide you with better service.

Unittus may store and process personal information in the United States and other countries.

####  Sharing Personal Information With Third Parties

Our Services allow you to share information about yourself with other individuals and other companies. Consider your own privacy and personal safety when sharing your information with anyone. Also, when sharing information about others, please consider their safety and privacy and get their consent for that sharing.

We do not share your personal information with third parties other than as follows:  

  * with your consent; for example, when you agree to our sharing your information with other third parties for their own marketing purposes subject to their separate privacy policies;
  * to (i) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, subpoena, legal process or other government request, (ii) enforce our Terms of Use Agreement, including the investigation of potential violations thereof, (iii) investigate and defend ourselves against any third party claims or allegations, (iv) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Unittus, its users or the public as required or permitted by law and (v) detect, prevent or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues;
  * in connection with any merger, sale of company assets, reorganization, financing, change of control or acquisition of all or a portion of our business by another company or third party or in the event of bankruptcy; and
  * with third party vendors, consultants and other service providers that perform services on our behalf, in order to carry out their work for us.

We may also share information with others in an aggregated form that does not directly identify you.

####  Choices

**Communications from Us.** You can opt out of receiving promotional messages from us, such as emails, by visiting the 'settings' page of your account. If you opt out of our promotional communications, we may still send you non-promotional messages about your account or our ongoing business relations.

**Cookies.** You can generally remove or block most cookies using the settings in your browser. In some cases, however, third party vendors may employ 'Flash' cookies to help us detect fraudulent or abusive uses of the Services and we or our third party advertisers may also use these cookies. If you choose to disable cookies, however, it may impact your ability to use our Services.

**Access to Your Information.** You may access and change your contact preferences and your information by visiting the 'Profile' and 'settings' sections of your account or by writing to us at the address provided below.

####  Security

Unittus takes reasonable measures to help protect your personal information in an effort to prevent loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction.

####  Persons Under the Age of 18

Persons under the age of 18 are not eligible to use our Services.

####  Your Obligations

As a subscriber, you have certain obligations to other subscribers. Some of these obligations are imposed by applicable law and regulations, and others have become commonplace in user-friendly communities of like-minded members such as Unittus:  

  * You must, at all times, abide by the terms and conditions of the then-current Privacy Policy and User Agreement. This includes respecting all intellectual property rights that may belong to third parties (such as trademarks or photographs).
  * You must not download or otherwise disseminate any information that may be deemed to be injurious, violent, offensive, racist or xenophobic, or which may otherwise violate the purpose and spirit of Unittus and its community of subscribers.
  * You must not provide to Unittus and/or other subscribers information that you believe might be injurious or detrimental to your person or to your professional or social status.
  * You must keep your username and password confidential and not share it with others.

Any violation of these guidelines may lead to the restriction, suspension or termination of your account at the sole discretion of Unittus.

####  Updates to This Policy

We reserve the right to modify this Policy from time to time. If we make any changes to this Policy, we will change the 'Last Revision' date below and will post the updated Policy on this page.

####  Contacting Unittus

If you have questions about this Policy, please contact us at [ compliance@Unittus.com.](mailto:compliance@Unittus.com)

This website is owned and operated, or operated under agreement, by:  
Unittus, Inc. 7353 International Place, Unit 309, Sarasota, FL 34240

Last Revision September 1, 2011

International Copyright © 2011 - 2015 Unittus, Inc. All rights reserved.

UNITTUS is a registered mark in the U.S. Patent and Trademark Office

This site and/or other services provided by Unittus are protected by one or more pending U.S. patent applications and includes “patent-pending” technologies.
